skybookmarks.com 2014-11-20

# Privacy Policy | skybookmarks.com

We are committed to protecting your privacy. We will only collect and use information about you lawfully. 

**Personal Information Collection**   
We collect only your name, e-mail address, submitted bookmarks and profile data. We care about the information we collect and it is used for helping you with the best possible services. We do not process this information in a way that is incompatible with this objective. 

**Protection of Personal Information**   
Your account information is protected by a password for your privacy and security. Protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer by logging off once you have finished using a shared computer. By visiting your User Profile, you can correct, amend, add or delete personal information on our website. You may request deletion of your account by visiting contact us page and sending email with detailed information. Please note that you will continue to receive all system e-mails (e.g. those regarding forgotten user passwords) and legal notices (e.g. updates to our policies) from us. 

We never share sensitive information about you without your explicit consent. We do not sell or pass any user's personal information, e-mail addresses included, to any other organization for any purpose. The information is held under high security and would not be shared for any reasons whatsoever. But we can sell our website with database at any time without prior notice. 

**Registration**   
In order for you to use website services, such as bookmarks new links to the website, you must complete a registration form. As part of this registration form, we require select personal information (including your full name, city, state and e-mail address). 

**User Profile**   
To allow you to express yourself beyond just the information collected during registration, we enable you to provide additional information, such as a bio, favorite URLs, and instant messaging IDs. You can control how your information is displayed and used. We are authorized to receive and record certain "traffic data" on their server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information, and the page you requested. We uses this traffic data to help diagnose problems with its servers, analyze trends and administer the website. We may collect and, on any page, display the total counts that page has been viewed. 

**Links to Other Sites**   
The website contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of such websites. Inclusion of links to an outside website, whether in an advertisement or content area of the website, is not an endorsement of the website or a guarantee that the information it contains is accurate. 

**Cookies**   
Cookies are text files stored on your computer when you visit web pages on our web site. This site uses cookies to improve your visit and to display relevant ads to you on third party web sites. 

**Children Under 18 Years of Age**   
You must be 13 years and older to register to use the website. As a result our site does not specifically collect information about children. If we learn that collected information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. 

**Conditions of Use**   
If you decide to visit our website, your visit and any possible dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of country law.
